<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title><![CDATA[!&amp;#]]></title>
    <link href="http://bangpound.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="http://bangpound.github.io/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-18T09:27:05+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bangpound.github.io/</id>
            <author>
            <name><![CDATA[Benjamin Doherty]]></name>                    </author>
        <generator uri="http://sculpin.io/">Sculpin</generator>
            <entry>
            <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYTHLYEEN! joins the call to nominate Frameline for S.F. Pride&#039;s Pink Brick Award]]></title>
            <link href="http://bangpound.github.io/blog/2014/02/10/Frameline"/>
            <updated>2014-02-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
            <id>http://bangpound.github.io/blog/2014/02/10/Frameline</id>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>FRAMELINE produces the San Francisco International LGBT Film Festival and their mission is "to change the world through the power of queer cinema" and yet...</p>

<p><strong>FRAMELINE has unquestionably caused serious harm to the LGBTQI community and our movement for equality by continuing to partner with the Israeli government.</strong> FRAMELINE does this in the face of a clear demand from Palestinian queers and a growing movement that they stand up for justice for Palestinians, queer and straight. In fact, FRAMELINE projects the logo of the Israeli Consulate at every one of the several hundred screenings at the festival. <strong>Most recently, Frameline refused to meet with Arab queers to even discuss this issue.</strong></p>

<p>The Pink Brick Award is given to individuals, organizations, businesses, etc… that have caused serious harm to the LGBTQ community or the LGBTQ movement for equality.</p>

<p class="lead">ARAB & ARAB AMERICAN QUEERS ASK YOU TO NOMINATE FRAMELINE for a Pink Brick Award by sending their name to SF Pride at <a href="mailto:gmnominations@sfpride.org">gmnominations@sfpride.org</a> TODAY.  Be sure to let them know you are nominating FRAMELINE them for their Pink Brick Award.</p>

<p>NOMINATIONS ARE DUE RIGHT AWAY</p>

<p>By it's persistence in a harmful relationship with the Israeli government, FRAMELINE has:</p>

<ul>
<li>marginalized queer Arab voices in our community</li>
<li>disrespected the queer Palestinian organizations and the pro-justice activists at home who have directly asked them to stop partnering with Israel</li>
<li>divided our communities</li>
<li>diminished the queer struggle for equality by aligning our movement with a policies that are based on inequality and oppression and yes, apartheid</li>
<li>hurt queer Palestinians (and Palestinians who are not queer) and their movement work</li>
<li>given in to Pinkwashing tactics use by those who want to portray queer identity as linked to racism, Zionism, and imperialism</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>About MYTHLLEEN!</strong> means homos in Arabic.  We are an international group of Arab &amp; Arab America Queers who work for justice including supporting the Palestinian Boycott Divestment and Sanctions (BDS) movement.</p>

<p><strong>About the PINK BRICK AWARD</strong>: The Pink Brick is a symbol of the first brick hurled at the Stonewall Riots in 1969. This faux award is an opportunity to highlight an individual or organization that has done significant harm to the LGBT community. It is also an opportunity to educate the community and the Pink Brick recipient about relevant issues.  Nominations are currently being accepted for the recipient of the 2014 Pink Brick. Nominations must be received by February 11.</p>

<p>NOMINATE FRAMELINE TODAY</p>
]]></content>
        </entry>
            <entry>
            <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pattern {P}³]]></title>
            <link href="http://bangpound.github.io/blog/2014/01/19/Pattern-{P}^3"/>
            <updated>2014-01-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
            <id>http://bangpound.github.io/blog/2014/01/19/Pattern-{P}^3</id>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<iframe class="embedly-embed" src="//cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=http%3A%2F%2Fplayer.vimeo.com%2Fvideo%2F84217154&src_secure=1&url=http%3A%2F%2Fvimeo.com%2F84217154&image=http%3A%2F%2Fb.vimeocdn.com%2Fts%2F460%2F991%2F460991058_1280.jpg&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=vimeo" width="700" height="394" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

<blockquote>
  <p>PARAMETRIC&#95;PALESTINIAN&#95;PATTERN {P}³</p>
  
  <p>The idea behind scripting a Palestinian pattern is to explore the potential of generating new patterns with a parametrical approach.</p>
  
  <p>An algorithm definition of {list&#95;item} and {shift&#95;list} was developed to retrieve items from a grid/list and to regenerate it into interesting patterns with a unique results.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>This comes from Vimeo user <a href="https://vimeo.com/user24276685">abboudeh</a>.</p>
]]></content>
        </entry>
            <entry>
            <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drufony]]></title>
            <link href="http://bangpound.github.io/blog/2014/01/14/drufony"/>
            <updated>2014-01-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
            <id>http://bangpound.github.io/blog/2014/01/14/drufony</id>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" lang="en"><p>Drufony is <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Drupal&amp;src=hash">#Drupal</a> 7 running in the <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Symfony&amp;src=hash">#Symfony</a> 2 framework. <a href="http://t.co/wo2KjvUCQV">http://t.co/wo2KjvUCQV</a></p>&mdash; Drufony (@Drufony) <a href="https://twitter.com/Drufony/statuses/422627353399808001">January 13, 2014</a></blockquote>

<script async src="//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
]]></content>
        </entry>
    </feed>